<krpano>

	<!-- du lieu chuyen ngu anh han -->
	<strings name="english"
		rotateButton = "Auto-rotation"
		fullsrButton = "Full screen"
		socialButton = "Share"
		nextButton = "Next scene"
		previousButton = "Previous scene"
		madebytext = "Produced by 360PRO.VN"
		autoPlayButton = "Auto-play"
		s0title = "Sebitsom"
		s0a1 = "Sebitsom entrance"
		s0a2 = "Sebitsom overview"
		texts0a1 = "[b]Sebitseom[/b][br/]
		[i]The three glowing islands that brighten the vista of the Han River![/i][br/][br/]
		Sebitseom is a cultural complex built to be a landmark on the Han River in the heart of downtown Seoul, a place where you can enjoy special cultural contents at the water’s edge. It is the world’s first floating structure with buildings that can float on water. Sebitseom consists of three glowing islands that brighten the Han River gloriously, along with Yevit, a place that screens a variety of video clips and contents.[br/]
		It symbolizes the life of Seoul citizens and illuminates Seoul and the Han River. chavit is, like the sun rising in the east, a glorious light that opens up a vibrant day. Solvit rises to the top and illuminates all directions like the sun at noon. Gavit shines beautifully and elegantly as it, like the sunset, puts the crowning glory on the day. The media art gallery Yevit will be a venue for art like the delicate moonlight illuminating the night."
		tickertexts0a1 = "Sebitseom is a cultural complex built to be a landmark on the Han River in the heart of downtown Seoul, a place where you can enjoy special cultural contents at the water’s edge. It is the world’s first floating structure with buildings that can float on water. Sebitseom consists of three glowing islands that brighten the Han River gloriously, along with Yevit, a place that screens a variety of video clips and contents. It symbolizes the life of Seoul citizens and illuminates Seoul and the Han River. chavit is, like the sun rising in the east, a glorious light that opens up a vibrant day. Solvit rises to the top and illuminates all directions like the sun at noon. Gavit shines beautifully and elegantly as it, like the sunset, puts the crowning glory on the day. The media art gallery Yevit will be a venue for art like the delicate moonlight illuminating the night."
		tickertexts0a2 = "Sebitseom is a cultural complex built to be a landmark on the Han River in the heart of downtown Seoul, a place where you can enjoy special cultural contents at the water’s edge. It is the world’s first floating structure with buildings that can float on water. Sebitseom consists of three glowing islands that brighten the Han River gloriously, along with Yevit, a place that screens a variety of video clips and contents. It symbolizes the life of Seoul citizens and illuminates Seoul and the Han River. chavit is, like the sun rising in the east, a glorious light that opens up a vibrant day. Solvit rises to the top and illuminates all directions like the sun at noon. Gavit shines beautifully and elegantly as it, like the sunset, puts the crowning glory on the day. The media art gallery Yevit will be a venue for art like the delicate moonlight illuminating the night."
		s1title = "some Gavit"
		s1a1 = "some Gavit"
		texts1a1 = "[b]some Gavit[/b][br/]
		[i]The island filled with luxurious and elegant light![/i][br/][br/]
		'some gavit' is a space filled with luxurious and elegant light. It has a convention hall optimized for MICE industries, with international conferences, corporate events, banquets and ceremonies, a cafe that over-looks the Han River, an Italian restaurant, and a pub/restaurant. A night in 'some gavit' is filled with beautiful lights. The LEDs that decorate the exterior give out splendid lights that accentuate the exclusivity and beauty of 'some gavit'."
		tickertexts1a1 = "'some gavit' is a space filled with luxurious and elegant light. It has a convention hall optimized for MICE industries, with international conferences, corporate events, banquets and ceremonies, a cafe that over-looks the Han River, an Italian restaurant, and a pub/restaurant. A night in 'some gavit' is filled with beautiful lights. The LEDs that decorate the exterior give out splendid lights that accentuate the exclusivity and beauty of 'some gavit'."
		s2title = "some Chavit"
		s2a1 = "some Chavit"
		texts2a1 = "[b]some Chavit[/b][br/]
		[i]The island full of bright and splendid joy![/i][br/][br/]
		'some chavit' is a space full of bright and splendid joy. chavit cuisine, where you can enjoy over 160 types of high-quality dishes, is a live buffet restaurant that offers a memorable dining experience with authentic cuisine and exquisite service. Retail shops will open on the first floor to provide you with not only the pleasure of dining, but also the excitement of shopping."
		tickertexts2a1 = "'some chavit' is a space full of bright and splendid joy. chavit cuisine, where you can enjoy over 160 types of high-quality dishes, is a live buffet restaurant that offers a memorable dining experience with authentic cuisine and exquisite service. Retail shops will open on the first floor to provide you with not only the pleasure of dining, but also the excitement of shopping."
		s3title = "some Solvit"
		s3a1 = "some Solvit"
		texts3a1 = "[b]some Solvit[/b][br/]
		[i]The the attractive and grand island![/i][br/][br/]
		'some Solvit' is a space filled with all kinds of pleasure with new events always going on. In this multi-purpose cultural space situated over water, we offer a venue for various interesting experiences such as exhibitions, performances and events. You can share some valuable moments with your loved ones as you take in the great open panorama of Hangang River."
		tickertexts3a1 = "'some Solvit' is a space filled with all kinds of pleasure with new events always going on. In this multi-purpose cultural space situated over water, we offer a venue for various interesting experiences such as exhibitions, performances and events. You can share some valuable moments with your loved ones as you take in the great open panorama of Hangang River."
	/>

	<strings name="korean"
		rotateButton = "자동 회전"
		fullsrButton = "전체 화면"
		socialButton = "몫"
		nextButton = "다음 장면"
		previousButton = "이전 장면"
		madebytext = "360PRO.VN에 의해 생산"
		autoPlayButton = "자동 재생"
		s0title = "세빛섬"
		s0a1 = "세빛섬"
		s0a2 = "세빛섬"
		texts0a1 = "[b]세빛섬[/b][br/]
		[i]한강을 아름답게 밝혀줄 세 개의 빛나는 섬[/i][br/][br/]
		세빛섬은 서울의 중심인 한강에 색다른 수변 문화를 즐길 수 있는 랜드마크로 조성된 복합 문화 공간입니다. 세계 최초로 물 위에 떠 있을 수 있는 부체 위에 건물을 짓는 플로팅 형태의 건축물입니다. 세빛섬은 한강을 아름답게 밝혀줄 세 개의 빛나는 섬과 다양한 영상 및 콘텐츠가 상영되는 예빛으로 이루어져 있습니다.[br/]
		서울 시민의 하루의 삶을 상징하며 서울과 한강을 비추고 있습니다. 채빛은 동쪽에서 떠오르는 해처럼 활기찬 하루를 여는 찬란한 빛입니다. 솔빛은 한낮의 해처럼 가장 높은 곳에 올라 온 사방을 비춥니다. 가빛은 해질녘 노을빛처럼 하루의 끝을 갈무리하며 아름답고 우아하게 빛나고 있습니다. 미디어아트갤러리 예빛은 밤을 비추는 은은한 달빛과 같은 예술의 장이 될 것입니다."
		tickertexts0a1 = "세빛섬은 서울의 중심인 한강에 색다른 수변 문화를 즐길 수 있는 랜드마크로 조성된 복합 문화 공간입니다. 세계 최초로 물 위에 떠 있을 수 있는 부체 위에 건물을 짓는 플로팅 형태의 건축물입니다. 세빛섬은 한강을 아름답게 밝혀줄 세 개의 빛나는 섬과 다양한 영상 및 콘텐츠가 상영되는 예빛으로 이루어져 있습니다. 서울 시민의 하루의 삶을 상징하며 서울과 한강을 비추고 있습니다. 채빛은 동쪽에서 떠오르는 해처럼 활기찬 하루를 여는 찬란한 빛입니다. 솔빛은 한낮의 해처럼 가장 높은 곳에 올라 온 사방을 비춥니다. 가빛은 해질녘 노을빛처럼 하루의 끝을 갈무리하며 아름답고 우아하게 빛나고 있습니다. 미디어아트갤러리 예빛은 밤을 비추는 은은한 달빛과 같은 예술의 장이 될 것입니다."
		tickertexts0a2 = "세빛섬은 서울의 중심인 한강에 색다른 수변 문화를 즐길 수 있는 랜드마크로 조성된 복합 문화 공간입니다. 세계 최초로 물 위에 떠 있을 수 있는 부체 위에 건물을 짓는 플로팅 형태의 건축물입니다. 세빛섬은 한강을 아름답게 밝혀줄 세 개의 빛나는 섬과 다양한 영상 및 콘텐츠가 상영되는 예빛으로 이루어져 있습니다. 서울 시민의 하루의 삶을 상징하며 서울과 한강을 비추고 있습니다. 채빛은 동쪽에서 떠오르는 해처럼 활기찬 하루를 여는 찬란한 빛입니다. 솔빛은 한낮의 해처럼 가장 높은 곳에 올라 온 사방을 비춥니다. 가빛은 해질녘 노을빛처럼 하루의 끝을 갈무리하며 아름답고 우아하게 빛나고 있습니다. 미디어아트갤러리 예빛은 밤을 비추는 은은한 달빛과 같은 예술의 장이 될 것입니다."
		s1title = "가빛"
		s1a1 = "가빛"
		texts1a1 = "[b]가빛[/b][br/]
		[i]고급스럽고 우아한빛이 가득한 섬[/i][br/][br/]
		가빛은 고급스럽고 우아한 빛이 가득한 공간입니다. 국제회의, 기업행사, 연회, 예식 등의 MICE 산업 개최에 최적화된 컨벤션홀 및 한강을 조망하며 즐길 수 있는 카페, 이탈리안 레스토랑, 펍 레스토랑 등이 입점되어 있습니다. 가빛의 밤은 아름다운 빛들이 가득합니다. 외관에 장식된 LED 가 화려한 빛을 발하며 가빛의 고급스러움과 아름다움을 더욱 돋보이게 합니다."
		tickertexts1a1 = "가빛은 고급스럽고 우아한 빛이 가득한 공간입니다. 국제회의, 기업행사, 연회, 예식 등의 MICE 산업 개최에 최적화된 컨벤션홀 및 한강을 조망하며 즐길 수 있는 카페, 이탈리안 레스토랑, 펍 레스토랑 등이 입점되어 있습니다. 가빛의 밤은 아름다운 빛들이 가득합니다. 외관에 장식된 LED 가 화려한 빛을 발하며 가빛의 고급스러움과 아름다움을 더욱 돋보이게 합니다."
		s2title = "채빛"
		s2a1 = "채빛"
		texts2a1 = "[b]채빛[/b][br/]
		[i]밝고 화려한 즐거움이 가득한 섬[/i][br/][br/]
		채빛은 밝고 화려한 즐거움이 가득한 공간입니다. 160여가지 이상의 수준 높은 요리를 즐길 수 있는 채빛 퀴진은 라이브 뷔페 레스토랑으로 메뉴 본연의 맛과 밝고 경쾌한 서비스를 통해 추억이 있는 식사를 즐기실 수 있습니다. 1층 chavit은 다양한 리테일샵이 입점되어 있는 복합문화공간으로 먹는 즐거음뿐만 아니라 쇼핑의 재미까지도 즐기실 수 있습니다."
		tickertexts2a1 = "채빛은 밝고 화려한 즐거움이 가득한 공간입니다. 160여가지 이상의 수준 높은 요리를 즐길 수 있는 채빛 퀴진은 라이브 뷔페 레스토랑으로 메뉴 본연의 맛과 밝고 경쾌한 서비스를 통해 추억이 있는 식사를 즐기실 수 있습니다. 1층 chavit은 다양한 리테일샵이 입점되어 있는 복합문화공간으로 먹는 즐거음뿐만 아니라 쇼핑의 재미까지도 즐기실 수 있습니다."
		s3title = "솔빛"
		s3a1 = "솔빛"
		texts3a1 = "[b]솔빛[/b][br/]
		[i]보기 좋고 훌륭한 섬[/i][br/][br/]
		솔빛은 항상 새로운 이벤트로 다채로운 즐거움이 가득한 공간입니다. 다목적 수상문화공간의 운영을 통해 전시, 공연, 이벤트 등의 다양하고 흥미로운 체험의 공간을 제공합니다. 가족, 친구, 연인과 함께 시원하게 트인 한강의 전경을 감상하며 특별한 순간을 나누실 수 있습니다."
		tickertexts3a1 = "솔빛은 항상 새로운 이벤트로 다채로운 즐거움이 가득한 공간입니다. 다목적 수상문화공간의 운영을 통해 전시, 공연, 이벤트 등의 다양하고 흥미로운 체험의 공간을 제공합니다. 가족, 친구, 연인과 함께 시원하게 트인 한강의 전경을 감상하며 특별한 순간을 나누실 수 있습니다."
	/>

</krpano>